Good evening.
Hey, hello, very good morning.
Feeling.
Hello.
Hey, hi, Shubhang, good. Hi, Karuna.
Hi, hi, Rajeev. Hi, Karuna. Hi, Rob.
Rob, do you want me to record this meeting or only transcribing is good enough?
Hey, hi, everyone.
I mean, as long as we transcribe, that's fine. I mean, if we want to record, we record. But I think transcription is at least enough.
Yeah, that that's my opinion also, Rob. Transcription would be good enough, rather than recording.
Okay.
Hope everyone in India had a good day and we are couple of more meetings and will be done with the day.
Okay, I guess Pankaj, you mentioned earlier, there is a conflict he may not be able to join. Shall we get going, everyone?
Okay, let me share my screen.
Yes, yes.
Yap.
Let me know once you are able to see my screen.
Yeah, Team, are you all able to see my screen?
Yes, Rajeev.
Okay, great, wonderful. So I am at the summary page as of now, but we will go through in details, right? So we have six stories in progress, two are done, and we still have 144 which are.
there in the backlog and there can be more additions in the due course.
Thanks.
Let me jump onto the boat.
Yeah, this is the current ongoing sprint zero, which is sprint one as such in the data.
The current status is 3 are done, 3 in progress and one to two. So let's look into that in details and see.
Yap.
Are you able to see this screen? This view?
It.
Yap.
OK, so three.
Tickets which are done is number 4, number 75, and number 78.
So, lay down the cloud code harness in the new repo.
This is done.
Get the POC in.
It just merged that this morning.
Get the POC in line is also done and the GitHub access.
So we can go through the rest of this open tickets and see which all can be marked on and which all will be rolled over into the next spring, which will be spring 2 starting from 7 September till 18 September. And then we will go through the backlog. We can.
You know, detail out the story or the ethics as a necessity.
with subtasks if required and pull them into the Sprint 2 for our focus area.
So one thing I want you to know is this is using like the default Jira profile. So right now, if you go into like the settings, ethics are above and are appearance to spikes, features, as well as user stories. I didn't know how to make the change to add like another level so that
That's to say like an epic is a parent of a feature, which is then a parent of a user story. So if you want to go, if you know how to make those changes, by all means, please do that. And then also just note that I only did epics and features here. So if we want to start using either user stories or subtasks then for the actual work, you know, I'll leave that up to you on how you want to run the board, but I'm just
Two, yeah.
You know, I just want to call it all the things from, you know, my bad PM management and setting up this, just so you know.
Right, see, we already have like, you know, if you see this scribble 75 is a feature, right?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Like, I have, I created a feature in a user story. I just didn't set up the hierarchy right. So right now you can't set, create a user story and have its parent be a feature because I didn't configure Jira to do that and I didn't know how to do that. So I'm just letting you know that if you want to set that up, you'll have to set that up.
And.
Okay.
So, I guess it means if I go back into the, you know...
Standard view, but...
See, here we all are, we are having all these epics and within epics we are having these stories, right?
Yeah, this view, right? And if you see, you know, feature is also as a work item. You know, epic is the parent and feature, story, task, bug item are the work items. So, you know.
We can create in between features if required and then make stories or tasks as part of the feature, right? That will become three level or it can become four level, like epic, then feature, then story, and then under story we can have tasks.
or subtasks. Let me show you another view.
Yes.
Yeah, so typically when good PMs that know what they're doing set that up for me, then yes, we have that structure. I'm just letting you know that I didn't know how to set that up when I got this board built, so that's just why it is the way that it is. So you'll just have to make those changes. So I'm just letting you know.
No, wait.
But, see, we, see, we should be good as of now to move forward with Epic and stories. Actually, stories, the work item as of now for us, and here, if you see, here is the, you know, example I was going through to...
Initiative at the very top level, which is like project or our the whole, you know, scribble is our initiative, then we have epics and within epics we are having the stories, even this one, right? Yeah, this one.
See, if we need, we can introduce features in between, between epics and user story, right? But as we already started, we are in the middle, let's move forward. And it will be like some more work for us to do, but you have already done a lot of things.
So, we can move forward with it, Rob. It, it, it should not impact us.
OK, OK, then coming back here, right to...
Cook.
Yeah, Shubhankar, I guess you are working on this one.
Where did you just start? Yeah.
Eighteen minutes.
The.
So, I, yeah, I have not put comment here, just so summary in the internal to review in within Team First. In summary, I was trying to figure out which devices we should introduce in our development and testing environments, so that we cover majority of performance and...
Will, will this be wrapped up?
And.
and application coverage over different OS versions. So my summary tells that.
We can go ahead with OIOS 16 as the base version because it covers 88% of the market as of now and majority of users are already using this OS version. Now coming to various devices, I would categorise these devices as form factors. So we have this small form factor like SE.
second generation iPhone, which is smaller, 4.5, 4.7 inch of screen, so that if anybody wants to use that device and draw, they should have a good visual experience while using this scribble application. And considering the regular devices like 14, 15, 16, 17.
Up.
all three variants and hence I have, you know, put in a summary in the channel. Once we all are aligned to that, I'll just put the comment in the ticket for review.
Songs: Yamadhi Shivani.
See you.
It, it just a proposal state right now, like...
Play.
Okay, so Shubhankar, yeah.
So, Pramod for...
Yes.
Sorry.
No, I just wanted to, like, should we should we for this MVP should we stick to like?
Right.
Else.
Like one version or...
Mm.
Is what I wanted to ask.
Soap.
Yeah, yeah, sure, sure. So that's a good question, like which version we should target first. So as I mentioned, like 16, we can set as a minimum version. So anything about running about 16, we can target. Like if we have a device running 16, that is fine because we can cheque how our application is behaving in that particular environment.
In general, I think more than 60% of the devices are already upgraded to 26. So that is like our go-to platform once we have like backward testing with 16. So the target would be the latest version which is running across majority of devices, that's 26.
But for backward compatibility, we target from 16, and that should be our ratio in that. And why I'm considering device form factor, because of our nature of application, like we have to draw something. So the visible space for end user, that should be properly usable for that, like.
Our application should render in that closed spaces as well.
So there are two different things now, like device size and the version support.
I hope that answers your question.
Yeah, I agree, but yeah, he wanted to hear from Rob and Pramod thoughts on this, yeah, yeah.
Surely, surely. Yeah, I think one more thing that just I missed. I think we can share the devices as one for each team, like as a developer may have a regular type of device like 14, 15, or 13 maybe. And the QA can have the lower version of the device to cheque all the bottlenecks or performance issues or...
do rigorous testing on that. And maybe we can have a higher end of device just to cheque how it is behaving with larger stream, the application. So I think that strategy we can follow, but it's up to conclude by all like what we should do. So that's all my proposal about it.
Yeah, so I think we probably don't want to get this into too much of A per item discussion because Rajeev, the intent was more on the board, but I think this one's good. Yeah, this one's an important one. So Rob, I think based on what Shubhankar has found, and I think he's probably also put it on the channel.
Yap.
Dave.
Exactly.
Leads.
Maybe we can make that recommendation of like base version, latest version, and basically setting the expectations that these will be the ones that we'll be focusing our testing on, maybe 3, 4 versions across this base to latest. And then we share it with Erik and group. That should be okay, right?
Proofs.
Yep, exactly. Let's get that in the meta repo as well. We'll have that documented on, you know, like create a page for it in the wiki. And then, yeah, we can get that in front of the client and then make sure they're approved, which they basically, they kind of do the same thing. So, yeah, no, sounds good.
Yeah, Shubhankar, actually this is not a technical discussion. We should stick at the high level status approach. Otherwise, we will always be short of time to conclude this meeting. Right. So my take is this will be.
Hey, uh, just sorry.
Sorry, I was a few minutes late. I just wanted to cheque whether we discussed the timelines, because there was that slight aberration, Rob, that where we had that seven day shape and the three sprints. Do we?
Hey.
Still keep that, or are we?
Given that you also scheduled the shape review tomorrow, are we still okay with the...
What was what was the timeline which was 7 and 10, 10 days or do we make it 10, 10, 10 by ending the sprint one on Friday? I don't know if you already discussed this, Rajeev.
No, I did not dis.
Because Jira, I think currently shows Jira currently shows September 4th as the sprint end.
Yap.
Mm.
Right, right, Pramod, I did not discuss on that, but as if we go with this plan, like complete sprint zero or sprint one in Jira by tomorrow, then the next sprint will go till late in September and and the.
For this printer, #3.
from Jira point of view will go till 2nd of October and the last sprint, so print #4 will be on 16th of October.
Right, what?
Yeah, so Rob, thoughts on that, ohh, about...
I think there was some rationale around having the first sprint zero at 7, maybe to align with reinvent timeline or something like that.
So remember, we're just on our first like 8 weeks and that's all we have the money for currently, even though they're raising more money so that then we can extend this out to like through reinvent and possibly past. So I mean, we can kind of make this however we want. The shape review, I'm literally just going to
Yeah.
Yes.
accumulate all of everything that you all have done in these last two weeks and just show that in front of the client and then just talk about what's next. So I mean, whether we schedule that next week or this week, it's up to us. I mean,
Yap.
And.
Got it. Yeah, but I was thinking, yeah, the other point that was there is given, like you said, 8 weeks is what this one is scheduled for, right? So I'm just thinking if on the boards, if we have it as seven and seven days print followed by.
Right, see, promote, yeah.
three, two weeks sprints. We may be a bit short of what the client was entitled for, even though we were working, we did the...
kick off on a Monday itself, but do you think from that perspective it makes sense to just have it as a full two-week sprint for shape?
Yeah, I mean, if we want, just adjust the date, let me know and we'll just call it out in the stand up and I'll move the shape review. Is that I'm perfectly fine. I'm just, you know, I was throwing this stuff out there, waiting for everybody else to help me adjust this. So thank you for helping me adjust this.
Yeah, yeah, I think...
See, if we, yeah, Pramod, if we go like this way, right, from 24th August to two weeks each, then we are ending on 16th of October, our spring #4, from Jira point of view, and that will be culmination of the project and
But...
So, you know, logical conclusion of eight weeks project.
Good.
When we can adjust, if you want, we can shorten this, you know, but in that case, we can't shorten it to before before today, we can we can complete this by today.
Then it will give us one day before.
Play.
So with everybody being out, or with some individuals being out tomorrow, I would actually lean towards, if we want to, I can move the shape review till later on next week. Just let me know when we want to end this first shape sprint, and then we can adjust all of our timelines.
Right.
I said a lot of this, you know, I was just throwing stuff down and just waiting for people to help me like correct these things. So yeah.
So I have no problems if we adjust these dates if we want to add and change that from being the end tomorrow to what ending next Tuesday.
No, that that will.
Yeah, I think tomorrow, yeah, tomorrow seems like a logical this thing. Maybe some of these items like the devices recommendation, et cetera, can also be got got into the some of these tickets and.
Updated, and we can probably so Rajeev, does that sound like a good plan? Yes, yeah.
Yap.
Yeah, yeah, Pramod, that is that is what I was understanding. If by tomorrow we can conclude these four open items, right? They do finalising on the device, right? And then Apple developer account setup is majority done, except maybe one or two individuals.
Which, Karuna, I guess you also have got it done today, right?
Yes, yes, that.
Okay, so this will also be done then the AWS access and cloud dev environment with the client. I guess this was also very close, so we can work with cheque with Pankaj and and this if this also gets done then the team.
Readiness, right, so, so we can complete this separate by tomorrow, logically conclude, right, whatever we want to.
share it with the client, we can.
Make it happen by tomorrow and then for Monday we can get going with so print 2 for which we will put all the items as we plan today.
Type T.
Which please feel free to create more of these planning sessions as you need them, or as we need them.
I will, yep, I will drop. I guess we might need a couple of more sessions. Only like one session for every separate will not suffice. We can have some, you know, technical sessions also as needed, but that I guess either Pankaj or yourself will have to drive it.
but I can help coordinating it.
Okay, okay team, let's then get going. Let's go look into the backlog and pull the items.
OK, so what? Let's start with this one.
AWS account and three environments. Can this go into the sprint number two, which we will be starting on Monday, and who to assign this?
Yeah, this is technically with the customer, Eric. So he was expecting at least the one environment, the development environment yesterday, but we still haven't got that. So hopefully we'll get an update today. But I think, yeah, part of it will flow into next trend, the setup of the QA and.
Yap.
broad environmental. I think we can have that continuing to the next.
Yeah.
OK, I'm moving it on placement.
Yes.
OK, the next two are already in progress, right? Karuna, you are working on this automation framework. It will it will go into sprint two.
Yes, yes.
Feel free to discuss if you have any question or any grooming is required.
Shah.
Do we want to throw that in sprint two or sprint one if it's in progress?
Oh, sprint one is.
Because we can always roll it if she needs longer. Oh, oh, right, right, right, sorry.
So, see, Sprint one is, I'm adding.
I was thinking it was a sprint zero, my bad.
Okay, so from today onwards, let's talk about Suprint one, two, three, and four. Let's forget about Suprint zero. I know in our SOW, it is a print zero, but we will stick with Jira nomenclature, right, to avoid any confusion.
Let me move this, so I can...
Mhm.
Okay, so Shubhankar, you are working on this, right? Client architecture and how it stays portable.
Yeah.
I'm moving this into stream two.
OK, and I know couple of items, Nitish, you are already assigned.
So.
If the status is, yeah, if the status is near closer, we can move them into sprint one, otherwise into sprint.
Yes, Rajeev.
So, Rajeev, these are actually from the decisions, and these are epics actually, and these just need like the scribble number 14, need certain command to close this one.
Mm.
So, these are spike tickets, right? This is spike tickets.
Well, it said, yeah, yeah, these are spike tickets currently that we are looking into, and this is something that decision is already made in the documentation, like scribble #14 requires a command, and I think we can close this one after that.
Yeah.
So can it happen by tomorrow? If yes, then we it will go into sprint one.
Let me just check, I think this is, I will cheque the description once more. I think this is all about the DynamoDB versus the Arora focus request that has already been decided.
And we can close it, yeah.
OK, we can move.
Let me then move it into sprint one, and once it you mark it close, it will be done. It will be, you know, completed with sprint one, otherwise it will roll over to sprint two. OK.
Suren.
Next one, this moderation, yeah.
Yeah, I know, I know Pankaj put a lot of, I know Pankaj put a lot of the documentation into the wiki already, so I think some of these might have already been closed. So yeah, Nitish, yeah, go through them and yeah, let's get all the ones closed so we can get those added to our sprint. Because yeah, I know our sprint, like we did way more than the six tickets that are showing up in there. We just weren't using the board. So yeah, so let's get that updated because he said, I'm going to be giving that to the client and being like, hey,
Right.
Yap.
Exactly, exactly.
Right.
We did all this awesome work, so yeah, let's make sure we can get, you know...
Actually, actually, if we look at all these spike tickets, originally they were planned for sprint zero, right?
Yeah.
But it is still there in the backlog. All these items from scribble 7 till scribble 17, right? They are part of E00, so print 0 as the tag.
Okay, Nitish covered this one, moderation fail policy.
So yeah, this one we actually discussed day before yesterday.
Mhm.
This would also require some comments over the ticket. We actually decided not to have the moderation policy.
Uh, but...
When today I was working on something, moderation is something been required by the Apple itself for application to go live on the Apple as discussed with Pankaj. So I just need to discuss one, this ticket again with Pankaj once before closing it.
OK, so you have time for that, by today or today, Babbar.
Yap.
This one relational data model Nitish.
Yes, this one I am working on, you can put it on a sprint too.
No.
How about this one back-end architectures find?
Yap.
I feel like Pankaj has already like done that one too. For right now, why don't we just skip the spikes and just focus on the getting things added to sprint two and then just have Pankaj review these spikes when he has a minute and then have him like update these because I feel like he's done the majority of these or we have documentation for them already.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, I will then then.
And some of them I just created just to, you know, flush out like, hey, we might need this, we might need this, and some of these we might not have needed. So just an FYI there too.
OK, how would this one CDK stack skeleton?
Who will take this up, Pankaj?
I think that this one will go to the DevOps.
Who is the DevOps person? It is.
One over.
Pramod, I think.
Mohamed. Mohamed.
Mohit is from our side.
Yeah.
Yes, yes.
Is not it?
He may not have been, so yeah, I think you can leave it unassigned. I think we might have to pull him in because he's been involved in the with Pankaj in discussing this, but I think with Sprint 2 we will he will he will be jumping on AWS and doing a lot of stuff, so.
With it.
OK, I move that item into this one. OK, let's go further.
Twenty-one.
Serverless API surface.
Can you just open it once, Rajeev? No, let me just click.
So I think this one needs to be updated because I could have swear Pankaj said that we're going to be using like some like a microservices for our API or I forget what he said we were using for our APIs and we're not going to use serverless. So I think this should need to be updated as well.
P.
So, can I assign this to Pankaj and move it into Sprint Two? We can update and either cancel it or...
Make the comments as necessity, right?
API contract and mog server.
Hi.
API contracts, there is one part that I am working on the API contract, but mock server I just saw today, it was created by Pankaj, but it was not today. I think some of the endpoints are still remaining. I think we can move it to spin too.
Will you take this up or Pankaj?
Yeah, you can assign it to me for right now.
Yap.
Media storage and delivery.
Nitish.
These are all part of backend work, but Rajeev, the point is...
Mmh.
How much we are going to take in the sprint, I am not sure about it. And there would be some sequential flow as well for the kind of work we will be doing. We can just pick something in between and start working on. They need to be API. I think that these are not in a sequence right now, the tickets.
Okay.
So.
because we might need to 1st create all the APIs and point it to be there only then these tickets should come up. Otherwise, randomly picking tickets would not work.
No, but Nitish, no matter what, you know, we majority of the work is going to happen through accelerator, right? Is NTKI.
OK, and in that way, you know.
We can look, we can look into this view right and see at epic level which epic we want, which which epic we want to do.
In this print one, sorry, so print two, and include all the all the stories belonging to that.
For example, if we are trying to do this one, this app big cloud foundation and app shell, so it means all these.
will go through. We can go into this way and update from here.
I'm okay with this approach.
Like, for example, this scribble 3 was meant for our shape.
Window, right?
Okay, let's talk about this auth and onboarding. Can it happen in this sprint? Sprint #2?
See, Nitish and everyone, we need to go with collective approach, right? I mean, whatever we are doing as of now was traditional approach method, but looking at the...
Uses of agentic AI.
We should go at high level. Here, we will try to complete this epic.
All together in.
Superint 2 or superint 3, right?
Otherwise, we have a long list.
And if we fail, you know, any of the epic, we should not be part of the MVP, right? It is optional or it is not.
So, mandatory, we can we can park it outside that will remain in the backlog.
See, otherwise time will fly away and we will not even realise what we are doing and where we are ending up in the sprint.
So I think there was some initial document Rob, right? I think that was initially about authentication that auth and...
Onboarding.
That was the initial document, if I remember correctly.
So I mean everything the wiki correlates with this Jira board because I built it all together.
One thing to remember is we still need to go through the epic one at the top there and make sure we get through all the epic one stuff. Yeah, yeah.
Yep, yep, yep, let's look into this.
I mean, these epics I did lay down in kind of an order where, I mean, like this first one is literally just laying down the ground, which is the app shell, the backend, the AWS surface.
I guess we should target all of it in our sprint #2, right?
Yeah, I think we already covered most of them, I think, except we were discussing scribble number 23 right now.
And.
That see, then that that that is what I'm saying. Like, if we decide this entire all, you know, this scribble one, right? We are we are doing it in Sprint 2, right? It doesn't mean it has to end within Sprint 2, right? There will be.
Mhm.
something which might left open which will roll over.
Mm.
Yap.
And then can we say that at this epic level, right? This one, right? If this is back end, then it is it is under your ownership, then Nitish, right?
Mhm.
Yap.
OK, OK, then we we are taking a call. This scribble one is going entirely right and.
No.
Yeah, it also contains.
The QA part as well, like the deploy automation, some other part of some contains the...
Play.
I will spa desert.
See, we we we can go through one by one, right? How about this one?
Mm.
AWS account and three environment. I guess we discussed this was an assigned to or this one.
Was with Client, right?
This can.
Give me on this file, look at CDK stack skeleton. We also discussed this was.
Mohamed.
Right, Mohamed, right? This, you are already working service server less API surface, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, this this needs updation of the.
Hello.
The content is not correct right now, and this ticket right, we need to update it.
So who will update that?
Now, you will update our Pankaj.
Initially.
Natixis.
Yeah, Rob initially created this, but now I, I'm not sure if I think Pankaj or Rob can update it, yeah.
I'm just gonna do that.
I think Pankaj, because right, I laid this down to the best of my abilities, but remember this is based off the prototype of my knowledge. You are the real experts that are laying down the real stack. So yeah.
Let me sign this to OK. How about this one? API contact and mock server.
I think this is already somewhere been done. You can assign it to Pankaj right now because this is, I think, been created what I saw today.
Otherwise, we can reassign to me the Pankaj as the Pankaj.
Okay.
Media and store media storage and delivery.
You can assign it to me.
Deploy automation.
I'm not sure. Again, can you just open the ticket once? What is in there?
I think it will be the DevOps. Yeah, CICD. So this also will be assigned to Mohit. So Rajeev, after the call, I think we can invite Mohit into the board and then assign to him.
Shibu.
Yap.
If you can send me the e-mail, I'll get it managed to the board.
We.
Yeah, I'll just message you.
I guess before that he might need to request for the Jira access.
Yeah, we need to see whether we already, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
OK, baseline observability about this Nitish.
Can you just open the ticket once?
Yeah.
I don't know why it is.
You probably just have to fly through this real quick just to get rid of it. Probably like your first initial, yeah.
Play.
OK, here we are, Natixis.
OK, let me just have a look.
Okay, I think this is all about logging.
Logs and observe will be on the back end.
Okay, you can assign it to me.
Okay.
OK, app shell routing and single brand thing.
I think this includes ROS changes.
You.
On the same thing.
Yeah, more of a application-related ticket.
So, who will take this up? You, Shubhankar?
Yes, please assign this to me.
OK, so this will go entirely. I will, you know, move them into...
OK, this we already talked about. Let's start with this on and onboarding.
And this going?
Sprint 2.
I think it will. Already Pankaj was doing research about the design and tools. So I think you can pull it in and then obviously, like you said, Pankaj can review it. He couldn't make it to the call right here. I think he'll review it and he can.
Mhm.
Right, we'll have to discuss with Pankaj separately, right? But like everything will go to Pankaj or in between there are things which will go to...
Justin.
Yap.
Different people.
I think this will be one that will be worked on as a course-grained item, one course-grained item. I don't think it will be piecemeal. So let's start with that and if Pankaj needs to, he can reassign.
OK, let me sign and get this.
Yap.
So while he's doing that, did we align on the end of our shape sprint? Are we saying shape ends tomorrow like I have it currently set, or are we wanting to extend that into next week?
Bhasin.
No, tomorrow was what we said, ending tomorrow, Rajeev. Yeah, yeah.
Okay, cool. I just want to double check. Okay.
Yeah.
OK, this question, then the next one is this daily prompt.
Can it happen? We can see if this is becoming a little heavy. We can circle back. It doesn't mean we need to complete or plan everything today. We can circle back on Monday again and go through, right? Even though we will start Sprint 2 with whatever we have.
Decided or planned already, so we can we can meet in between, you know, Monday or Tuesday, Wednesday, whenever.
Comfortable, we can, you know.
Along with Pankaj, we can reiterate.
Yap, I think that makes sense.
Looks like it is becoming a little heavy as of now and Pankaj is not there in the meeting and that is creating a gap also.
Yes, and uh, what I think some of this, this like...
Mmh.
This epic daily prompt, this would be something where developer and back end and the front end would be.
We both need to be worked on a similar ticket or separate tickets need to be graded.
Somehow, somewhere.
Hey.
Well, we can create subtasks on them. So I just create subtasks for that and at that point then just to sign up the subtasks then to the individual roles.
On some of these.
So, in this story, you are saying there are some tasks present right now, and it's like scribble number thirty-five.
No, see this, this is.
No, I'm saying you'll have to create them. I only created it at an epic and a feature level or epic and user story, feature, whatever.
OKOK, fine.
Right.
Toth.
Right, right, within story, like you know, if it is assigned to you, Nitish, and you need somebody else to work partly on that.
Good.
MM.
Stars or sub-tasks can be created and assigned.
Yap.
And actually, you know, let me be very frank here. We may not focus too much on, you know, what we are doing in data versus what we are doing actually on the...
Work front, right? Jira can be here and there. Jira can remain at high level when we will not go into the details. We will rely more upon code base and how we are moving forward with the PR and doing some automation such a way that.
When the code is getting updated, PR is getting moved, the Jira should move its status from in progress to done.
Yap.
Okay.
But, but look at this and take take this as a high level, you know, a direction for us to move forward collectively, right?
And Rob, I guess if you haven't heard me, in case you were on break, we were discussing if it is becoming a little heavy as of now for us to plan and decide everything for sprint two. We will circle back again, maybe early next week.
Along with Pankaj and reiterate.
Yeah, go ahead. Yeah, please put the please put a follow-up meeting on our calendars for that. Yeah.
We will, we.
Exactly, I will do that. I will do that after checking availability from Pankaj, because he is must to be there in this meeting.
How do you do?
I think once the team starts looking at the current set of stories that we put out there, I think they'll realise that some of this work has already been done. And so a lot of it will just be like, oh, we just need to do this little part and this little piece. And so yeah, I think we're a lot further. It's just right now, we're just throwing the whole backlog at you and it just, it's overwhelming.
Yap.
Yes, yes.
Good.
Exactly, exactly. That's what I'm feeling. It is becoming a little heavy as of now, but once we start moving, you know, we will try moving big, big things together. You know, like at the epic level, we will try to make the progress.
Using agentic AI rather than individual and detail level.
Rob, one request I asked from my end. So actually I was going through the some of the user stories and epics as well. The terminology when I go through it is little, I seem to be.
Not able to make it or tough to understand. Is there a way we can simplify this information we have in this user stories or epic, say example, like one which is like pure specific, sorry, Rajeev, I just.
Shibu.
We have scribble 54 which I was going through for the QA foundation standards and like there is a lot of information and we are also have some interlinks with the other information as well. So yeah, like this is one example, but there are a few other also I see.
If there is a way we can have these requirements more simplified version.
I mean, you can feel free to break these down, like, you know, use Claude, you know, hey, this, you know, let's break this story down or, well, I think this epic, that's the epic. So I was trying to put as much detail in the epic, right, and then break that out into multiple like lower level tasks that then can be more easily accomplished and more.
Yeah, this is epic.
Yeah.
Yeah, smaller thing. So is that feel free, is that I laid down what I could, and that's where unfortunately y'all will have to go back over it and then adjust it to y'all's desires in months.
Mm.
Like, should we do this like manually individual or we have to use meta report to do this, like update the details with it?
Sleep.
Really.
See, we already...
If you want to do it with Claude, use the meta repo because it has the built-in commands in there and it's also everything that's backed in here is tied to the wiki. So like when you click on them and you go to like the bottom of them, it should have like links. It'll take you directly into the wiki where either pointed at
Mm.
pajunks like architecture, like documentation or as references, or we're pointing to a specific screen where, you know, I just showed you like the prototype, where I have the prototype and all the screens laid out and then all the documentation, because I didn't want to like copy everything out and then have two sources of truth. So there's a lot of pointing back to the meta repo. So I would highly recommend using the meta repo when you're editing and playing with Jira, because a lot of the details in.
Correct, correct.
The wiki.
Okay. Okay.
Sure, I like I could see there are sub tasks, but Rajeev, there is like not only this, but I was looking through the epic that we talked about, auth and onboarding. I did go through only a couple of them today to like understand. I'm trying to relate with the workflows also that we have.
Yap.
in the meta repo, but yeah, I see this like little challenge to make it out.
Yeah, as I said, feel free to take those and rewrite them. As I said, I mean, I even make assumptions on, you know, from my viewpoint of what QE should be doing. So by all means, as I said, make these your own. If it's not worded correctly, word it how you want it to be corrected. As I said, I was trying to play everybody's role and, you know, I'm only so good.
Mm.
No, I understand. No, no, that's where I wanted to bring this up and then take your suggestion. Yeah, so that like we have, I mean, like this is all again a base, even whatever we want to drive for the, whether it's a development or testing, it drives from here.
Right, so I wanted to cheque with you and take your suggestion. But yeah, whatever information here, it is definitely helpful. That is a direction. We have direction from here. Thank you.
Pardon.
Okay, anything else, team? We still have 5, 7 minutes before our stand up.
Okay, then, Team, we can wrap up this meeting, take a short break, a couple of minutes, and circle back for the standard.
And for the stand-up, can we show the, when you're running, can you show the board so we can use that as like our, I don't know, how are we going to do it?
Rick.
Yeah, yeah, sure, right? We we can we can refer the board and go through, you know, the updates using board that will be, you know, much better way to understand things and it will enhance our communication and collaboration.
Perfect.
Perfect. Awesome. See everybody in 5 minutes.
Okay, then. Thanks. Thanks, everyone.
Thanks, bye.
Thanks, all. Bye.
Thank you.
Cheers, bye bye.